Hey all and welcome back to my channel.
So in this video I'll be sharing how I
cleared or how I got selected for ICLI
bank uh for the role of relationship
[music] manager and for the grade deputy
manager 2 uh with ascent program which
is ICSA ascent program and I'm a 2026
PAT student and ICSA bank had conducted
on campus placements recently and I got
selected. So in this video I'll be
explaining about uh the selection
process and what all rounds we have and
how I successfully cracked this uh job
[snorts] and uh all those things I'll be
explaining this video. So make sure to
watch this video till the end. Let's get
started. [music]
So after we apply to the program or
after we apply uh in the official ICA
bank carriers portal uh the first round
is online questionnaire plus profile
completion. So in this round what we
need to do is we just basically we need
to you know fill the profile details
with accurate details and at the end we
will be asked some queries uh like um
why do you want to join ICA bank? we
just need to type it. Okay. So like that
five or six questions will be there and
it is uh you know pretty easy like uh
mostly everyone will get shortlisted for
this because it's just you need to fill
everything perfectly and make sure you
have 100%age in profile completion and
the next round is aptitude. So aptitude
round is where the major elimination
happens like only half of the students
from the online questionnaire or the
from the first round were selected in
the second round. So in aptitude round
the questions were like easy to medium
level only and it will be happening in a
virtual way and we will be having the
topics like quantitative ability,
logical thinking and also at the end uh
we will have to you know speak on two
topics which are given on the screen and
your video will be also recorded along
with that. So that's how the aptitude
round happened and it's pretty easy if
you prepare well and those who are
selected from the aptitude round were
called for an in-person interview um by
the HR managers of ICICI bank. So
talking about the in-person interview uh
the HR will be asking banking based
questions and also situation based
questions and also your background. They
will ask about your self intro um like
um about your background from where are
you coming your family members and also
they expect a good communication
confidence and also make sure that uh
you know you answer to everything in a
positive way so that um they know that
you are genuinely interested in this
carrier and also they will ask more like
uh are you okay with sales because
relationship manager is is a salesorient
oriented job. So make sure that uh you
have also prepared for answering related
to that and they will ask uh are you
okay to relocation and all those things
and that's it. So after completing the
interview like after two weeks I
received a mail from our official campus
uh placement that I am uh successfully
clear I got selected for relationship
manager in ICA bank and uh along with me
many candidates have also selected and
yeah I'm happy for it and so yeah so if
you are a person who really want to
crack ICA bank as the relationship
manager then make sure you follow
everything that I have mentioned in this
video and yeah that's it so there is
another thing this is ascent program
this is not aspire program so I don't
know what's the difference between
aspire and ascent but uh for our campus
it was written as ascent program bya
bank so that's it guys you can easily
crack this interview easily if you have
prepared you have that confidence you
have good communication and you have a
good dress code then I'm sure that
you'll be you know getting cracked
easily. So all the best. So do comment
down your queries and subscribe to my
channel for more placement related
videos [music] and thank you.